A Guide to the Thomas H. Hunter Collection 1934-1995
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO CHEVES MCC. SMYTHE 1966/09/14, TL (CC) (Box-folder 15-67)
- CHEVES MCC. SMYTHE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966/09/07, TLS (Box-folder 15-68)
- LEE POWERS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966/08/08, TLS (Box-folder 15-69)
- RUSSELL C. MILLS TO MARTIN G. NETSKY 1968/02/05, TL (CC) (Box-folder 15-70)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO JOHN PARKS 1968/01/12, TL (CC) (Box-folder 15-71)
- JOHN PARKS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1967/12/21, TLS with AA (Box-folder 15-72)
- INSTITUTE ON INTERNATIONAL MEDICAL EDUCATION PRELIMINARY PROGRAM 1966/03/27-30, Printed Program (Box-folder 15-73)
- ROBERT A. MOORE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1965/11/19, TLS (Box-folder 15-74)
- JAMES P. DIXON TO ROBERT A. MOORE 1965/07/05, TL (CC) (Box-folder 15-75)
- ROBERT A. MOORE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966/02/18, TLS with AA (Box-folder 15-76)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO ROBERT A. MOORE 1966/02/21, TL (CC) (Box-folder 15-77)
- KENNETH HOLLAND TO WARD DARLEY 1966/02/01, TLS (Box-folder 15-78)
- THOMAS B. TURNER TO SIR ARCOT L. MUDALIAR 1966/01/24, TL (P) (Box-folder 15-79)
- A. L. MUDALIAR TO THOMAS B. TURNER 1966/01/02, TLS (P) (Box-folder 15-80)
- JOHN A. D. COOPER TO ERNANI BRAGA 1964/07/06, TL (CC) (Box-folder 15-81)
- VERNON E. WILSON TO HAYDEN C. NICHOLSON 1967/06/26, TLS (CC) (Box-folder 15-82)
- HAYDEN C. NICHOLSON TO VERNON E. WILSON 1967/06/14, TL (CC) (Box-folder 15-83)
- THOMAS B. TURNER TO VERNON E. WILSON 1967/06/05, TLS (P) with TN (Box-folder 15-84)
- SHERMAN M. MELLINKOFF TO VERNON E. WILSON 1967/05/29, TLS with AA (Box-folder 15-85)
- SHERMAN M. MELLINKOFF TO VERNON E. WILSON 1967/05/29, TL (CC) (Box-folder 15-86)
- WILLIAM G. ANLYAN TO VERNON E. WILSON 1967/05/30, TL (CC) (Box-folder 15-87)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO JOHN L. CRANER 1966/10/05, TL (CC) (Box-folder 15-88)
- JOHN L. CRANER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966/09/29, TLS (Box-folder 15-89)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO JOHN W. V. CORDICE 1966/06/01, TL (CC) (Box-folder 15-90)
- JOHN W. V. CORDICE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966/05/23, TLS (Box-folder 15-91)
- JOHN W. V. CORDICE TO ROBERT A. MOORE 1966/05/10, TL (CC) (Box-folder 15-92)
- SHERMAN M. MELLINKOFF TO VERNON E. WILSON, VERNON E. WILSON TO SHERMAN M. MELLINKOFF 1967/11/14-28, 2 TLS (P) with TN (Box-folder 15-93)
- JOHN MAIER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/04/14, TLS (Box-folder 15-94)
- JOSEPH D. BEASLEY 1969/04/11, TLS (Box-folder 15-95)
- R. T. RAVENHOLT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/04/22-24, TLS with AN (Box-folder 15-96)
- R. T. RAVENHOLT TO HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE 1969/04/04, TL (P) (Box-folder 15-97)
- THE AGENCY FOR INTERNATIONAL DEVELOPMENT POPULATION AND FAMILY PLANNING PROGRAM - GOALS, SCOPE, AND PROGRESS BY R. T. RAVENHOLT 1969/03, Reprint (Box-folder 15-98)
- THE TRAGEDY OF THE COMMONS BY GARRETT HARDIN 1968/12/13, Reprint (Box-folder 15-99)
- ROBERT W. BABIONETO, ROBERT J. GLASER, AND THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/04/15, TNS (CC) (Box-folder 15- 100)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO MORTON LEVITT 1969/04/11, TL (P) (Box-folder 15- 101)
- ERNEST GARDNER TO ROBERT J. GLASER 1969/03/ca, TLS (P) (Box-folder 15- 102)
- MORTON LEVITT TO ROBERT J. GLASER 1969/01/21, TLS (P) (Box-folder 15- 103)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO ALAN GUTTMACHER 1969/04/10, TL (P) (Box-folder 15- 104)
- PHYLLIS SHEETZ TO LUCILLE S. BLOCH 1969/04/18, TL (CC) (Box-folder 15- 105)
- LUCILLE S. BLOCH TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/04/14, TLS (Box-folder 15- 106)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO CLARK E. VINCENT 1969/04/18, TL (CC) (Box-folder 15- 107)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO RICHMOND K. ANDERSON ET. AL. 1969/04/01-07, TL wit AA and AN (Box-folder 15- 108)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO RICHMOND K. ANDERSON ET. AL. 1969/04/10, TL (Box-folder 15- 109)
- ROBERT J. GLASER TO GEORGE T. HARRELL 1969/04/04, TLS (P) (Box-folder 15- 110)
- GEORGE T. HARRELL TO ROBERT J. GLASER 1969/04/02, TLS (P) (Box-folder 15- 111)
- LUCILLE S. BLOCH TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/04/01, TLS with AA (Box-folder 15- 112)
- BROOKS RANNEY TO GEORGE JAMES 1969/03/27, TLS (P) (Box-folder 15- 113)
- JOHN A. D. COOPER TO OSCAR HARKAVY 1969/03/18, TL (P) (Box-folder 15- 114)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/03/18, T Memo (Box-folder 15- 115)
- LUCILLE S. BLOCH TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/03/10, TLS (Box-folder 15- 116)
- EQUILIBRIUM 1966 DEATH TABLE N.D., AMs (Box-folder 15- 117)
- LOUISE W. KEADY TO LUCILLE S. BLOCH 1969/03/05, TLS (P) (Box-folder 15- 118)
- ROBERT JOY GLASER - BIOGRAPHICAL SKETCH 1969/01, TMs (P) (Box-folder 15- 119)
- ABRAHAM HORWITZ - CURRICULUM VITAE N.D., TMs (P) (Box-folder 15- 120)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO R. T. RAVENHOLT 1970/02/02, TL (CC) (Box-folder 15- 121)
- INSTITUTE ON MEDICAL EDUCATION AND FAMILY PLANNING - LIST OF PARTICIPANTS AND DISCUSSION GROUPS 1969/03/ca, TMs (P) (Box-folder 15- 122)
- INSTITUTE ON MEDICAL EDUCATION AND FAMILY PLANNING - LIST OF PARTICIPANTS AND DISCUSSION GROUPS 1969/03/ca, TMs (P) with AA (Box-folder 15- 123)
- GORDON T. STEWART TO HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE 1969/02/26, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-1)
  AAMC 17 (Association of American Medical Colleges)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO MARGARET MEAD 1968/12/30, TL (P) (Box-folder 16-2)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO MCGEORGE BUNDY 1968/12/30, TL (P) (Box-folder 16-3)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO MERLIN K. DUVAL 1968/12/30, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16-4)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO [ ? ] 1968/12/30, TL (P) (Box-folder 16-5)
- ROBERT C. BERSON TO JOHN M. WEIR 1968/11/22, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-6)
- JOHN PARKS TO ALLAN C. BARNES 1968/05/29, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-7)
- CORRECTION 1968/06/04, T Memo with AA (Box-folder 16-8)
- GORDON MEIKLEJOHN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/02/28, TLS with AA (Box-folder 16-9)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO HALSTED R. HOLMAN 1969/03/04, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-10)
- HALSTED R. HOLMAN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/02/18, TLS (Box-folder 16-11)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO E. CROFT LONG 1969/03/04, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-12)
- E. CROFT LONG TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/02/19, TLS (Box-folder 16-13)
- C. G. GRULEE TO HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE 1969/02/22, TLS (CC) (Box-folder 16-14)
- ASSOCIATION OF AMERICAN MEDICAL COLLEGES DIVISION OF INTERNAL MEDICAL EDUCATION INSTITUTE ON MEDICAL EDUCATION AND FAMILY PLANNING N.D., TMs (P) (Box-folder 16-15)
- LIST OF INTERNATIONAL GUESTS N.D., TMs (P) (Box-folder 16-16)
- PAUL N. YLVISAKER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/01/20, Telegram (P) (Box-folder 16-17)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO KIRK T. MOSLEY 1969/01/23, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-18)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO ROBERT A. MOORE 1969/01/10, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-19)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO JOHN Z. BOWERS 1969/01/10, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-20)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO CLYDE V. KISER 1969/01/14, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-21)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO JOSEPH R. DIPALMA 1969/01/14, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-22)
- "AGENCY FOR INTERNATIONAL DEVELOPMENT'S FAMILY PLANNING STRATEGY" BY R. T. RAVENHOLT 1969/01/10, Reprint (Box-folder 16-23)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO W. G. ANLYAN 1969/01/13, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-24)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO PAUL YLVISAKER 1969/01/06, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-25)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO RAYMOND L. VANDE WIELE 1969/01/06, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-26)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO KATHERINE B. OETTINGER 1969/01/13, TL (P) (Box-folder 16-27)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO LEE M. HOWARD 1969/01/03, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-28)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO R. T. RAVENHOLT 1969/01/03, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-29)
- ROBERT A. MOORE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/01/02, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16-30)
- JOHN Z. BOWERS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/01/02, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16-31)
- E. CROFT LONG TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/12/30, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16-32)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/12/31, TLS (Box-folder 16-33)
- MEMO OF MEETING, ASSOCIATION OF AMERICAN MEDICAL COLLEGES OFFICE 1968/12/18-27, T Memo (P) with AA and AN (Box-folder 16-34)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/12/17, TLS (Box-folder 16-35)
- GENERAL INFORMATION BULLETIN 1969/03/23-26, T Memo (P) (Box-folder 16-36)
- TENTATIVE SUBSTANTIVE PROGRAM 1969/03/23-26, T Memo (P) (Box-folder 16-37)
- "THE TRAGEDY OF THE COMMONS" BY GARRETT HARDIN 1968/12/13, Reprint (Box-folder 16-38)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO CARMEN A. MIRO 1968/12/12, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-39)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO JORGE VILLAREAL MEJIA 1968/12/12, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-40)
- NEWS RELEASE - HARVARD UNIVERSITY 1968/11/26, TMs (P) (Box-folder 16-41)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO MCGEORGE BUNDY 1968/11/22, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-42)
- LOUIS HELLMAN TO D. A. CAHAL 1968/11/21, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-43)
- D. A. CAHAL TO L. HELLMAN 1968/11/15, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16-44)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO ROBERT EBERT 1968/11/21, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-45)
- ROBERT H. EBERT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/11/18, TLS (Box-folder 16-46)
- "LEVI, INSTALLED AS UNIVERSITY OF CHICAGO PRESIDENT, VOICES DOUBT ON VALUE OF MUCH IN GRADUATE EDUCATION", FREDERICK C. ROBBINS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/11/15, 19, Newspaper Clipping, TLS with AA (Box-folder 16-47)
- LUCILLE S. BLOCH TO HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE, ET. AL. 1968/11/14, T Memo (CC) (Box-folder 16-48)
- LUCILLE S. BLOCH TO HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE ET. AL. 1968/11/14, T Memo (CC) (Box-folder 16-49)
- GEORGE JAMES TO CARMEN A. MIRO 1968/11/13, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-50)
- LOUIS HELLMAN TO PHILIP CORFMAN 1968/11/11, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-51)
- LOUIS HELLMAN TO DENNIS A. CAHAL 1968/11/11, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-52)
- LOUIS HELLMAN TO DAVID CLARK 1968/11/11, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-53)
- LOUIS HELLMAN TO BENJAMIN PECKHAM 1968/11/11, TL (P) with AA (Box-folder 16-54)
- ROBERT W. BABIONE TO FREDERICK C. ROBBINS 1968/11/06, TL (P) (Box-folder 16-55)
- ROBERT W. BABIONE TO ROBERT W. GILLESPIE 1968/11/06, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-56)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO MEMBERS OF STEERING COMMITTEE 1968/ca, TL (P) (Box-folder 16-57)
- LINCOLN GORDON TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/10/28, TLS with AA (Box-folder 16-58)
- MEMORANDUM OF MEETING 1968/10/22, T Memo (P) with AA (Box-folder 16-59)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO RICHMOND ANDERSON ET. AL. 1968/10/ca, TL (P) (Box-folder 16-60)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO CHARLIE, GEORGE, FRED 1968/10/ca, 3 TL (P) (Box-folder 16-61)
- MEMBERS OF THE STEERING COMMITTEE 1969, TMs (P) with AN (Box-folder 16-62)
- MEMORANDUM OF MEETING 1968/10/25, T Memo (P) with AA and AN (Box-folder 16-63)
- FIRST MEETING OF THE STEERING COMMITTEE 1968/10/18, T Memo (P) with AN (Box-folder 16-64)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/10/14, TLS with AA (Box-folder 16-65)
- JOHN PARKS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/10/11, TLS (Box-folder 16-66)
- JOINT MEETING OF SUBJECT COMMITTEES 1968/10/11, TMs (P) (Box-folder 16-67)
- GEORGE JAMES TO LUCILLE S. BLOCH 1968/10/07, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16-68)
- ANNOTATED PROGRAM - ASSOCIATION OF AMERICAN MEDICAL COLLEGES INSTITUTE ON MEDICAL EDUCATION AND FAMILY PLANNING 1968/10/17, TMs (P) (Box-folder 16-69)
- MEMORANDUM OF MEETING 1968/09/26-10/02, T Memo (P) with AN (Box-folder 16-70)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO CARMEN MIRO 1968/09/25, TLS (P) with AN (Box-folder 16-71)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO MARGARET MEAD 1968/09/27, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-72)
- MARGARET MEAD TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/09/20, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16-73)
- KURT L. GOLDSTUECKER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/09/24, 30, TLS (P) with AN (Box-folder 16-74)
- MEMORANDUM OF MEETING 1968/09/20, T Memo (P) (Box-folder 16-75)
- FREDERICK C. ROBBINS TO MEMBERS OF SUBJECT COMMITTEE I 1968/09/20, T Memo (P) (Box-folder 16-76)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO CARL E. TAYLOR 1968/09/12, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-77)
- CHARLES C. SPRAGUE TO MEMBERS OF SUBJECT COMMITTEE III 1968/09/11, T Memo (P) (Box-folder 16-78)
- MEMORANDUM OF MEETING 1968/09/10, 19, T Memo(P) with AN (Box-folder 16-79)
- MARGARET MEAD TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/09/09, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16-80)
- THE INSTITUTE ON MEDICAL EDUCATION AND FAMILY PLANNING 1968/09/09, TMs (P) (Box-folder 16-81)
- GEORGE JAMES TO MEMBERS OF SUBJECT COMMITTEE II 1968/09/05, T Memo (P) (Box-folder 16-82)
- GEORGE L. HARPER TO GEORGE JAMES 1968/09/04, T Memo (CC) (Box-folder 16-83)
- GEORGE JAMES TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/05/20, 22, TLS (P) with AN (Box-folder 16-84)
- CARL E. TAYLOR TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/08/15, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16-85)
- ROBERT W. BABIONE TO INSTITUTE ON MEDICAL EDUCATION AND FAMILY PLANNING 1968/08/26, 09/03, T Memo (P) with AA and AN (Box-folder 16-86)
- GEORGE JAMES TO MEMBERS OF SUBJECT COMMITTEE II 1968/09/05, T Memo (P) (Box-folder 16-87)
- JOHN MAIER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/08/29, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16-88)
- LESLIE CORSA TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/08/29, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16-89)
- MARY F. DEAN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/08/29, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16-90)
- ROBERT W. BABIONE TO INSTITUTE ON MEDICAL EDUCATION AND FAMILY PLANNING 1968/08/26, T Memo (P) (Box-folder 16-91)
- BARBARA I. ZIEGLSCHMID TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/08/21, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16-92)
- ALLAN C. BARNES TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/08/18, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16-93)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO ROBERT C. COOK 1968/06/22, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-94)
- CATHERINE COUGHLIN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/08/16, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16-95)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO LOUIS M. HELLMAN 1968/08/15, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16-96)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO RAYMOND L. VANDE WIELE 1968/08/15, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16-97)
- CARL E. TAYLOR TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/08/15, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16-98)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO GEORGE JAMES 1968/08/15, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16-99)
- GEORGE JAMES TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/08/08, 12, TLS (P) with AN (Box-folder 16- 100)
- JOHN M. CHAPMAN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/08/14, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16- 101)
- JOHN M. CHAPMAN TO CHARLES C. SPRAGUE 1968/08/14, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16- 102)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO SUBJECT COMM. II MEMBERS 1968/08/14, TL (P) (Box-folder 16- 103)
- JORGE VILLAREAL MEJIA TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/08/14, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16- 104)
- RAYMOND L. VANDE WIELE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/08/12, TLS (P) (Box-folder 16- 105)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO SUBJECT COMM. II MEMBERS 1968/08/12, TL (P) (Box-folder 16- 106)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO MARGARET MEAD 1968/08/09, TL (CC) (Box-folder 16- 107)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO MARGARET MEAD 1968/08/02-05, TL with AA and AN (Box-folder 17-1)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO MALCOLM MERRILL 1968/08/02, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-2)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO LEE HOWARD 1968/08/02, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-3)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO RICHMOND ANDERSON 1968/08/01, TL (CC) with TA (Box-folder 17-4)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO FREDERICK C. ROBBINS 1968/08/05, TL (CC) with TA (Box-folder 17-5)
- MEMORANDUM OF MEETING - POPULATION COUNCIL 1968/08/08, T Memo (Box-folder 17-6)
- SHELDON J. SEGAL TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/08/07, TLS (P) (Box-folder 17-7)
- RICHMOND K. ANDERSON TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/08/06, TLS (P) (Box-folder 17-8)
- JOSEPHINE CADUNZI TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/08/06, TLS (P) (Box-folder 17-9)
- MEMBERS OF THE STEERING COMMITTEE 1969, TMs (P) (Box-folder 17-10)
- "POPULATION - STILL EXPLODING" BY WILLIAM M. DRAPER N.D., Reprint (Box-folder 17-11)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO JORGE VILLARREAL MEJIA 1968/08/01, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-12)
- CAROL DELAY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/08/07-09, TPC with AN (Box-folder 17-13)
- J. RICHARD UDRY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/08/31, TLS (P) (Box-folder 17-14)
- CAROL DELAY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/08/19-22, TPC (P) with AN (Box-folder 17-15)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO CARMEN A. MIRO 1968/07/31, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-16)
- MEMBERS OF THE STEERING COMMITTEE 1969, TMs (P) (Box-folder 17-17)
- ALONZO S. YERBY TO HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE 1968/07/31, TLS (P) (Box-folder 17-18)
- ROBERT C. COOK TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/07/26, TLS (P) (Box-folder 17-19)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO LOUIS M. HELLMAN 1968/07/26, TLS (P) (Box-folder 17-20)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO RAYMOND VANDE WIELE 1968/07/26, TLS (P) (Box-folder 17-21)
- ALONZO S. YERBY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/07/24, TLS (P) (Box-folder 17-22)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO ALONZO S. YERBY 1968/07/26, TL (P) (Box-folder 17-23)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO LOUIS M. HELLMAN 1968/07/26, TLS (P) (Box-folder 17-24)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO ROBERT C. COOK 1968/07/22, TL (P) with AA (Box-folder 17-25)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO SUBJECT COMM. III MEMBERS 1968/08/12-22, TL (P) with AN (Box-folder 17-26)
- DAVID E. PRICE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/07/22, TLS (P) (Box-folder 17-27)
- WILLIAM H. DRAPER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/06/27, TLS (Box-folder 17-28)
- WILLIAM H. DRAPER TO JOHN PARKS 1968/06/27, TLS (P) (Box-folder 17-29)
- JOHN PARKS TO WILLIAM H. DRAPER 1968/05/29, TLS (P) (Box-folder 17-30)
- WILLIAM H. DRAPER TO HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE 1968/05/ca, TLS (P) (Box-folder 17-31)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO WILLIAM H. DRAPER 1968/06/13, TLS (P) (Box-folder 17-32)
- GEORGE JAMES TO HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE 1968/06/18, TLS (P) (Box-folder 17-33)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO ALLAN C. BARNES ET. AL. 1968/06/13, TL (Box-folder 17-34)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO JOHN PARKS 1968/06/13, TL (P) (Box-folder 17-35)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO CHARLES C. SPRAGUE 1968/06/13, TL (P) (Box-folder 17-36)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO COLIN MACLEOD 1968/06/13, TL (P) with TA (Box-folder 17-37)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO FREDERICK C. ROBBINS 1968/06/05, TLS (P) with AA (Box-folder 17-38)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO ERNEST GRUENING 1968/05/22, TL (P) with AA (Box-folder 17-39)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO ROBERT C. BERSON 1968/05/14, T Memo (CC) with AA (Box-folder 17-40)
- ROBERT C. BERSON TO EXECUTIVE COUNCIL 1968/05/14, T Memo (P) (Box-folder 17-41)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO KATHERINE OETTINGER 1968/05/13, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-42)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO JOHN MAIER 1968/05/13, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-43)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO LEE HOWARD 1968/05/13, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-44)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO JAROSLAV HULKA 1968/05/13, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-45)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO JOSEPH A. CAVANAUGH 1968/05/13, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-46)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO RICHMOND ANDERSON 1968/05/13, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-47)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/04/17, TLS with AA (Box-folder 17-52)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/04/16, TLS with AA (Box-folder 17-53)
- JACK D. LANGE TO HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE 1969/05/26, TLS (Box-folder 17-54)
  AAMC 18 (Association of American Medical Colleges)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO LUCILLE S. BLOCH 1969/05/23, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-55)
- LUCILLE S. BLOCH TO HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE 1969/05/20, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-56)
- SOMS - UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA 1969/ca, TMs (P) (Box-folder 17-57)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO DAVID FROST 1969/04/03, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-58)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO MEMBERS OF COMMITTEE ON INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS IN MEDICAL EDUCATION COMMITTEE 1969/04/25, T Memo (P) (Box-folder 17-59)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO LIAISON OFFICERS FOR INTERNATIONAL ACTIVITIES 1969/04/25, T Memo (P) (Box-folder 17-60)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO EDWIN FONDO 1969/01/02, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-61)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO EDWIN FONDO 1968/12/31, TL (P) (Box-folder 17-62)
- PHYLLIS SHEETZ TO HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE 1968/12/30, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-63)
- EDWIN FONDO TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/12/23, ALS (Box-folder 17-64)
- MCGEORGE BUNDY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/12/18, TLS (Box-folder 17-65)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO MCGEORGE BUNDY 1968/12/30, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-66)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966/05/09, TLS (Box-folder 17-67)
- M. E. LAPHAM TO THOMAS B. TURNER 1966/04/07, TLS (CC) with AA (Box-folder 17-68)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO MAX E. LAPHAM 1966/04/11, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-69)
- ROBERT A. MOORE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966/04/06, TLS (Box-folder 17-70)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO ROBERT A. MOORE 1966/04/11, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-71)
- MARY B. WIEDRICH TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966/04/07, TLS with AA (Box-folder 17-72)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO ROBERT MORISON 1966/04/11, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-73)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO WALSH MCDERMOTT 1966/04/11, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-74)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO LEONA BAUMGARTEN 1966/04/11, TL (CC) (Box-folder 17-75)
- REVISED TABLE OF CONTENTS 1966, TMs (P) with AA (Box-folder 17-76)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO STEERING COMMITTEE, HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO COMMITTEE ON INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS IN MEDICAL EDUCATION 1964/12/22, 2 T Memo (P) (Box-folder 17-77)
- ASSOCIATION OF AMERICAN MEDICAL COLLEGES INSTITUTE ON INTERNATIONAL MEDICAL EDUCATION STEERING COMMITTEE 1966/ca, TMs (P) with AA (Box-folder 17-78)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO STEERING COMMITTEE 1965/10/04, T Memo (P) (Box-folder 17-79)
- ASSOCIATION OF AMERICAN MEDICAL COLLEGES INSTITUTE ON INTERNATIONAL EDUCATION STEERING COMMITTEE 1965/04/21, TMs (P) (Box-folder 17-80)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO STEERING COMMITTEE 1965/03/16, T Memo (P) with AA (Box-folder 17-81)
- AN INVENTORY OF SELECTED COMMUNITY MEDICAL PROGRAMS AND ACTIVITIES OF THE NEW YORK HOSPITAL - CORNELL MEDICAL CENTER N.D., TMs (Box-folder 17-82)
  AAMC 19 (Association of American Medical Colleges)
- GLEN R. LEYMASTER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972/05/10, TLS (Box-folder 17-83)
- MARJORIE P. WILSON TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972/05/30, TLS (Box-folder 17-84)
- CORNELL UNIVERSITY ANNOUNCEMENTS GRADUATE SCHOOL OF MEDICAL SCIENCES 1971-1972 1971-1972, Pamphlet (Box-folder 17-85)
- CORNELL UNIVERSITY MEDICAL COLLEGE/1971 1971, Pamphlet (Box-folder 17-86)
- CORNELL UNIVERSITY ANNOUNCEMENTS MEDICAL COLLEGE 1971-1972 1971-1972, Pamphlet (Box-folder 17-87)
- FOLDER CONTAINING THOMAS H. HUNTER'S MATERIALS FOR CORNELL VISIT 1972/ca, Printed Folder (Box-folder 17-88)
- REPORT TO THE DEAN BY THE MEDICAL COLLEGE COMMITTEE ON GOVERNANCE 1972/04/03, TMs (P) (Box-folder 17-89)
- J. ROBERT BUCHANAN TO DALE R. CORSON 1971/08/23, TL (P) (Box-folder 17-90)
- FACULTY HONORS 1971/ca, TMs (P) (Box-folder 17-91)
- OUTSTANDING EVENTS 1971/ca, TMs (P) (Box-folder 17-92)
- CENTERSCOPE 1972/05, Pamphlet (Box-folder 17-93)
- AUGUST H. GROESCHEL TO CENTRAL PLANNING GROUP 1972/06/06, T Memo S (P) (Box-folder 17-94)
- "WALTER GELLHORN RETIRES FROM THE BOARD 1971/ca, Reprint (Box-folder 17-95)
- ANNUAL REPORT OF THE SOCIETY OF THE NEW YORK HOSPITAL 1971, Pamphlet (Box-folder 17-96)
- "THE SAMUEL J. WOOD LIBRARY N.D., Pamphlet (Box-folder 18-1)
- NAMETAGS FOR THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., Printed Forms (3) (Box-folder 18-2)
- AMERICAN MEDICAL ASSOCIATION-ASSOCIATION OF AMERICAN MEDICAL COLLEGES LIAISON COMMITTEE SURVEY TEAM VISIT 1972/06/ca, TMs (P) (Box-folder 18-3)
- BULLETIN AND CALENDAR OF EVENTS 1972/06/05-12, Pamphlets (2) (Box-folder 18-4)
- "MINORITY GROUP STUDENT PROGRAMS AT C. U. M. C." BY JAMES L. CURTIS 1971/ca, Reprint (Box-folder 18-5)
- CORNELL UNIVERSITY MEDICAL COLLEGE ALUMNI QUARTERLY 1972/ca, Pamphlet (Box-folder 18-6)
- THE NEW YORK HOSPITAL NEWS 1972, Pamphlet (Box-folder 18-7)
- MEETING OF SURVEY GROUP AND SITE VISITORS: SOMS 1969/02/09, TMs (P) (Box-folder 18-8)
- STUDIES IN FAMILY PLANNING 1969/02, Pamphlet (Box-folder 18-9)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/03/03, TLS with AA (Box-folder 18-10)
- TENTATIVE SUBSTANTIVE PROGRAM 1968/12/31, TMs (P) (Box-folder 18-11)
- DR. HUNTER'S LIST OF PROFESSORS OF MEDICINE N.D., TMs with AA (Box-folder 18-12)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO ROBERT W. BABIONE 1969/02/18, TL (CC) (Box-folder 18-13)
- LLOYD H. SMITH TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/02/14, TLS (Box-folder 18-14)
- RICHARD V. EBERT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/02/10, TLS (Box-folder 18-15)
- LOUIS G. WELT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/02/10, TLS (Box-folder 18-16)
- WILLIAM B. BEAN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/02/10, TLS (Box-folder 18-17)
- ALEXANDER LEAF TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/02/10, TLS (Box-folder 18-18)
- ALEXANDER G. BEARN, WILLIAM B. BEAN, AND ROBERT G. PETERSDORF TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/02/ca, 3 PC with AA (Box-folder 18-19)
- ROBERT G. PETERSDORF TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/02/10, TLS (Box-folder 18-20)
- DONALD W. SELDIN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/02/08, TLS (Box-folder 18-21)
- ROBERT W. BABIONE TO ALFRED J. BOLLET 1969/02/03, TL (P) (Box-folder 18-22)
- ROBERT W. BABIONE TO KURT W. DEUSCHLE 1969/02/03, TL (CC) (Box-folder 18-23)
- ALEXANDER G. BEARN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/02/07, TLS (Box-folder 18-24)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO HERBERT L. LEY 1969/02/05, TL (P) (Box-folder 18-25)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO LLOYD H. SMITH 1969/02/04, TL (CC) (Box-folder 18-26)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO DUDLEY KIRK 1969/01/31, TL (CC) (Box-folder 18-27)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO EARL SIEGEL 1969/01/31, TL (CC) (Box-folder 18-28)